今晚多干点活吗？
like to be a little more involved tonight?
检查一下气球 彩带 烟火？
Supervise the balloons, the streamers, the fireworks?
- 好吧 -嗯？
- All right. - Yeah?
你知道我对这些很有品位
You know I got an eye for that.
这就是为什么我是个好摄影师
That's why I'm such a good photographer.
-当然 好的 -我喜欢烟火
- Absolutely. Yeah. - And I love fireworks.
声音啊 光芒啊
The noise, the lights.
基本上就这些
Mostly those aspects.
好吧 听着 我一会把细节发给你
All right, look, I'm gonna text you about this later.
我现在得走了 这个替罪羊跑不了了
Right now I've gotta go. This goat's not gonna scape itself.
感觉我被迫害了
I feel persecuted.
我就在坐等被媒体扔进池子里
I'm just waiting for the press to throw me in a pond
看我能不能自己漂起来
to see if I'll float.
蜜月期(第一个月)结束了 是吧？
Honeymoon's over, isn't it?
不过蜜月也跟坨屎似得
It was kind of a shitty honeymoon, too.